<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuide</string>
    <string name="list">list</string>
    <string name="name">Rajahmundry</string>
    <string name="pla_godavari">Godavari River</string>
    <string name="pla_gowthami">Gowthami Ghat</string>
    <string name="pla_iskon">Iskon Temple</string>
    <string name="pla_pushkar">Pushkar Ghat</string>
    <string name="pla_twin">Twin Bridges</string>
    <string name="pla_bridge">Road cum Railway Bridge</string>
    <string name="pla_info_twin">Thses twin bridges are the links between east godavari and west godavari. One of the bridge was closed and another one was still running. Both these bridges are railway bridges which distances about 2.4 kms wach.</string>
    <string name="pla_info_pushkar">Pushkar city houses 52 Bathing Ghats (bathing places). The city also has the only shrine dedicated to Lord Brahma in the whole of India. The sacred Pushkar Lake is also believed to have great healing and purifying powers. As a result, a pilgrimage tour is often considered incomplete without a holy dip from any of the various Bathing Ghats in Pushkar. A dip in its holy waters during the eve of Kartik Poornima is regarded auspicious.</string>
    <string name="pla_info_gowthami">There are numerous things to see and experience in Gowthami Ghat,rajahmundry, provided you have the right information. With a host of exciting things to do in Gowthami Ghat,rajahmundry, travelers can thoroughly enjoy the experience of exploring this destination. If you are travelling for the first time, the Gowthami Ghat,rajahmundry travel guide may help resolve most of your queries about Gowthami Ghat,rajahmundry. In fact, it is like a veritable information packed handbook on Gowthami Ghat,rajahmundry tourism. All you need is a list of options on topics such as where to stay, what to eat, weather in Gowthami Ghat,rajahmundry and places to visit in Gowthami Ghat,rajahmundry</string>
    <string name="pla_info_godavari">The Godavari is Indias second longest river after the Ganga. Its source is in Triambakeshwar, Maharashtra.The river upon reaching the plains begins to widen out until it reaches Rajamundry.</string>
    <string name="pla_info_iskon">International Society for Krishna Consciousness (ISKCON) world wide organization, which is a non profit, social welfare and spiritual organization engaged in propagating the teachings and values of the great ancient literatures of our Vedic heritage.</string>
    <string name="pla_info_bridge">The Godavari Bridge or Kovvur Rajahmundry Bridge is truss bridge spanning Godavari river in Rajahmundry, India. It is Asias third longest road cum rail bridge crossing a water bodyThe bridge is 4.1 kilometers (2.8 km Rail part, 4.1 km Road part) long consisting of 27 spans of 91.5 m and 7 spans of 45.72 m of which 6 spans of 45.72m are in 6 deg. curve at long Rajahmundry end to make up for the built up area. The bridge has a road deck over the single track rail deck, similar to the Grafton Bridge in New South Wales, Australia. This bridge, in addition to Godavari Arch Bridge, has been widely used to represent Rajahmundry in arts, media, and culture. It is one of the recognised symbols of Rajahmundry.</string>
    <string name="intro">Rajahmundry, officially known as Rajamahendravaram, is a city in the Indian state of Andhra Pradesh located on the banks of the Godavari River in East Godavari district.The city is known for its historic traditional, cultural, agricultural and economic backgrounds and hence, it is known as the Cultural Capital of Andhra Pradesh.</string>

    <string name="res_avakai">Avakai Hotel</string>
    <string name="res_dfc">Deccan Fried Chicken</string>
    <string name="res_shelton">Shelton Hotel</string>
    <string name="res_sri_kanya">Sri Kanya Restaurant</string>
    <string name="res_venky">Venkies Delight</string>
    <string name="res_info_avakai">Avakai restaurant was located near godavari. It was a pure veg restaurant which was famous for avakai biryani. All types of veg items are available here.</string>
    <string name="res_info_dfc">DFC is known for Deccan Fried Chicken which is similar to KFC. It was a non veg restaurant. They sell only items that are made with chicken. It was located at AV apparao road.</string>
    <string name="res_info_shelton">It was the richest hotel in rajahmundry. It was located at thadithota near RTC complex. They deliver to home for free. It was a 3 star hotel. All types of items are available here.</string>
    <string name="res_info_sri_kanya">Sri Kanya Hotels are available at many places in rajahmundry. They are serving almost all in every part of the city. This restaurant was famous for tasty food. All types of items are available here.</string>
    <string name="res_info_venky">Venkies Delight was also famous for tastty food. They sell both veg and non veg items. Thay serve people very fastly.</string>

    <string name="hot_sitara">Sitata</string>
    <string name="hot_info_sitara">Spoil yourself in 3 star riverfront luxury at Hotel Sitara Grand, Rajahmundry Spare contemporary design makes your room a calm haven, and picture windows offer you dazzling views. Rise and shine with a dip in the holy river and breakfast with ample choice of the lavish South Indian and North Indian Cuisine at Hotel Sitara Grand. Contemporary interiors are complemented by international and Indian cuisine available for room delivery with WIFI access. Located near to Rail, Road, Airways, this budget hotel emerges as one of the most conveniently accessible for the tourists coming to Rajahmundry.</string>
    <string name="hot_shelton">Shelton Hotel</string>
    <string name="hot_info_shelton">Shelton Rajamahendri features a spa and massage center, fine dining at Citrus and drinks at the Sphere lounge and Twister sports bar. Location: Hotel Shelton Rajamahendri, Rajahmundry, Andhra Pradesh is located in the scenic Eastern Godavari region. </string>
    <string name="hot_sri_grands">Sri Grands</string>
    <string name="hot_info_sri_grands">Hotel is very near to bus complex manager is friendly staff are good and polite service is quick and good but there is no restaurent but on call they will provide everything rooms are clean. Really the Environment of Hotel is too Good.. Regarding House Keeping, Way of Receiving , The Hotel in the City Center , Mostly the Service and The Quality Maintenance is TO GOOD. Really the KING SIZE DOUBLE BED ROOM having same Like as Shelton r any other 3 star Hotel</string>
    <string name="hot_venky">Venkies Delight</string>
    <string name="hot_info_venky">Featuring free WiFi, Venkys Delight is set in Rājahmundry. This 2 star hotel offers room service and valet parking. The hotel offers an Indian restaurant. At the hotel, the rooms come with a desk. Every room includes air conditioning and a flatscreen TV, and certain rooms at Venkys Delight have a city view.A vegetarian breakfast is available every morning at the property.</string>

    <string name="hos_kims">KIMS</string>
    <string name="hos_info_kims">KIMS Bollineni Hospital has a department of causality that is fully equipped to manage any type of emergency conditions before referring them to a specific department or any other Intensive Care Unit. Department of causality has the following equipment to handle various types of emergencies. causality processes are designed to ensure seamless patient treatment across various departments within the hospital and react quickly to any type of medical requirement, which may be needed by the patient.</string>
    <string name="hos_raju_neuro">Raju Neuro Hospital</string>
    <string name="hos_info_raju_neuro">Raju Neuro and Multi Speciality Hospital in Rajahmundry. Hospitals with Address, Contact Number, Photos, Maps. View Raju Neuro and Multi Speciality Hospital in Rajahmundry, Raju Neuro and Multi Speciality Hospital is a recognized name in patient care. It was incepted in the year 1993. They are one of the well-known Hospitals in Gandhipuram. Backed with a vision to offer the best in patient care and equipped with technologically advanced healthcare facilities, they are one of the upcoming names in the healthcare industry. Located in , this hospital is easily accessible by various means of transport. A team of well-trained medical staff, non-medical staff and experienced clinical technicians work round-the-clock to offer various services that include Visitors Timings 00:00, Pathology Lab , Ct Scan , Mri Scan </string>
    <string name="hos_apex">Apex Hospital</string>
    <string name="hos_info_apex">Started in 2005 with the sole intention of providing the highest quality Surgical care to the population of the Godavari districts at affordable prices, Apex hospitals has since risen to be one of the most reputed hospitals in the Godavari districts. We have an excellent team of doctors from specialties including General surgery, Anaesthesiology, orthopaedics visiting specialists from Plastic Surgery, Neurosurgery, surgical oncology, nephrology offering a wide range of  High risk Surgical and Emergency treatment options including Intensive care. We have over 50 in patient rooms, a 5 bed step down unit, an OR with advanced Laparoscopic capabilities, a 10 bed ICU equipped with mechanical ventilators and staffed by an Anesthesiologist 24×7.</string>
    <string name="hos_chakra">Chakradhar Hospital</string>
    <string name="hos_info_chakra">It is often said that nothing happens, unless there is a dream first. At the genesis of the chakradhar hospitals story there was a dream. A dream so powerful, that it helped transform the medical landscape in Rajahmundry. The dream nurtured and grew within very few years, the founder Chairman of chakradhar hospitals , until the point of inflection happened in 2008. Today, with over 60 beds and a significant presence at every touch-point of the medical value chain,chakradhar Hospitals is one of rajahmundrys largest healthcare groups. Commenced as a 60 bed hospital, today the group has grown exponentially in rajahmundry Its growth is often said to be synonymous with rajahmundry emerging as a major hub in global healthcare.</string>
</resources>
